[Music]
[Música]
let's see Loli a little, who the
vamos a ver un poco a Loli que que el
other day was also talking about
otro día estuvo hablando también de
taking down my channel, I'm going to show you
tirarme el canal os voy a enseñar de
how to do a strike, I totally think it
cómo hacer strike totalmente creo que
could be very well brought but the
puede estar muy bien traído pero que el
issue of taking down a channel I mean you can
tema de tirar un canal O sea tú puedes
sue obviously and you can and you
demandar evidentemente y te puedes y
can put 18 lawsuits against a person
puedes ponerle a una persona 18 demandas
as many as you want but already
todas las que tú quieras pero ya
organize know how to take down a channel that already
organizar sepa tirar un canal eso ya
has a series of you know I was
tiene una serie de sabes lo estuve
seeing it with Pablo and with and with my other
viendo con Pablo y con y con mi otro
lawyer and we have man we have
abogado y tenemos hombre tenemos
planned that it could happen they want to see you
previsto que puede pasar te quieren ver
on the street Javi exactly Ana we have
en la calle Javi exactamente Ana tenemos
planned that it could happen because we are dealing with
previsto que pueda pasar porque estamos
people that we are dealing with people that we
ante gente que estamos ante gente que
can find ourselves
puede con la que nos podemos encontrar
with this any day you understand
con esto cualquier día me entiendes
So
Entonces
mm in the event that it happens there are a
mm en el caso de que pase es que hay una
series of consequences also penal and
serie de consecuencias también penales y
some stories lucrative there are some
unas historias lucro sante hay unas
things there, that thing is already out of my
cosas ahí lo de eso ya se me va de las
hands there is already out of my hands
manos ahí ya se me va de las manos
because that is when I see them capable
porque ahí ya es cuando los veo capaces
of making any mistake because she
de cometer cualquier error porque ella
says she assumes that she loses the
dice ella da por hecho que pierde el
channel first Why does she assume that she
canal primero Por qué da por hecho que
loses the channel because she knows
pierde el canal porque sabe
perfectly warned I think  that because they've
perfectamente avisado yo creo que porque
warned her, of course, I think it's
le han avisado claro yo creo que es
because she knows perfectly well that if you
porque sabe perfectamente que si tú
play dirty with YouTube's rules,
juegas sucia con las normas de YouTube
the one who gets sanctioned is her, the one who gets
al que sancionan es a ella a la que la
sanctioned is her, but r I was
sancionan es a ella pero r estaba
pointing out something else and it's that I think it's
apuntando otra cosa y Es que creo que es
possible that she already has some warning from
posible que tenga ya algún aviso de
YouTube and therefore
YouTube y por lo tanto
uh we're talking about her
eh estemos estemos hablando de que su
channel being compromised, it's very good apt,
canal esté comprometido es muy buen apta
says Karime, don't even say it as a joke
dice Karime no lo digas ni de broma
Karime, no, it's not a thing that I
Karime yo no no es una cosa Que que
rule out eh Knowing how the
descarte eh Sabiendo Cómo está la
circumstance is m I you guys are
circunstancia m Yo ustedes lo estáis
living it with me day to day eh besides
viviendo conmigo al día a día eh además
that you have a company with employees,
que tú tienes una empresa con empleado
leaving so many people on the street, no no,
dejar a tanta gente en la calle no no
but it's not that, but there are
pero no es eso sino que eso hay
consequences, man, let's see, you
consecuencia hombre vamos a ver tú no
can't give me a strike on a
puedes ponerme a mí un strike en un
video when I'm telling you months
vídeo cuando yo te estoy diciendo meses
before that whenever you want, I'll remove it for
antes que cuando quieras lo quito por
good reason if I'm telling you,
las buenas si yo te estoy diciendo a ti
let's see, family, this, this is
vamos a ver familia esto Esto es de
logical, this no longer requires a
lógica esto ya no hace falta ni sea
lawyer or anything like that, okay, if I
abogado ni nada por el estilo vale si yo
'm telling you for good reason,
a ti te estoy diciendo por las buenas
Hey, we can each take our own
Oye podemos tomar cada uno Nuestro
path and leave each other alone, what do you want me to
camino y dejarnos en paz qué quieres que
remove  all the videos I remove all
quite todos los vídeos yo quito todos
the videos and every tweet I've posted
los vídeos y cada tweet que haya puesto
about you and you say No no no no no it's no
sobre ti y tú dices No no no no no me
good to me the video doesn't bother me I
vale a mí no me molesta el vídeo Yo
want you to lose your channel and you
quiero que te quedes sin canal y tú
go and start reporting every
coges y empiezas a reportar todos los
day all my channels all my videos
días todos mis canales todos mis vídeos
until you leave me without a channel and you walk
hasta que me dejas sin canal y te paseas
around the entire internet saying that I have to be
por todo internet diciendo que hay que
kicked off YouTube that you want to take down my
echarme de YouTube que quieres quitarme
channel that it's justified that my
el canal que está justificado que mi
family doesn't eat contacting one
familia no coma contactando con una
person with another person with another man what do you
persona con otra persona con otra hombre
think happens well there are
ustedes qué creéis que pasa pues hay
consequences Of course they are no longer
unas consecuencias Claro que ya no son
issues of the right to honor you know Then
temas de derecho al honor sabes Entonces
I have already
yo ya os he
told you I think that since I don't
dicho yo creo que el que ya que no hace
need to tell you anything else but it is
falta que os diga más nada pero es así
exactly like that tesa I mean how are you going to
exactamente tesa O sea tú cómo vas a
eliminate a channel for a video that they
eliminar un canal por un vídeo que te
are telling you for good Hey let's
están diciendo por las buenas Oye vamos
remove it and each one goes their own way
a quitarlo y cada uno toma su camino
then there you are already doing you know you
entonces tú ahí ya estás haciendo sabes
have to resist Javi María del Mar I
hay que resistir Javi María del Mar yo
resist what I try to do is comply with
resisto yo lo que intento es cumplir con
the rules and man Ray of my Consuelo
las normas y hombre Ray de mi Consuelo
is that I do not see a kiss my Consuelo
es que no me aparece un beso mi Consuelo
we have to make a Corrillo we have to
tenemos que hacer un Corrillo tenemos
make a huddle I know I have to
que hacer un Corrillo lo sé que tengo
make a huddle I always
que hacer un Corrillo que siempre lo
say it and in the end I never do it the
digo y al final nunca lo hago yo lo
only thing I ask of you please is all the
único que Os pido por favor es todo el
support you can not only
apoyo que podáis tanto ya no solamente
with the box and with the objectives but
con la caja y con los objetivos sino
above all
sobre todo
join the WhatsApp group
e meteros en el grupo de WhatsApp
follow me on Twitter on Instagram on
seguirme en Twitter en instagram en
Facebook follow me everywhere because
Facebook seguirme en todas partes porque
if they manage to eliminate me from somewhere
si me consiguen eliminar de alguna parte
then we'll be in another place okay look at my
pues estaremos en otra vale mira mi
Carmen from October every day she does her
Carmen de octubre cada día hace su
superchat eh but not me where do they have
superchat eh pero no a mí a donde tienen
Carmen the box has sat on them like
que Carmen la caja les ha sentado como
a firecracker where their back loses its
un petardo donde la espalda pierde su
chaste name face rolling with
casto nombre cara revolviéndose de la
laughter face rolling with laughter face rolling with laughter face rolling with
risa cara revolviéndose de la risa cara
laughter I don't know if we
revolviéndose de la risa yo no sé si si
should make an extract commenting on
deberíamos hacer un extracto comentando
all of them what they have said about
todos ellos lo que lo que han hablado de
the box all of them because of course now we would have to
la caja todos ellos porque claro ahora
now We would have to see all of
habría que ahora Habría que ver a todos
them if they say the same thing about the box dard
ellos si dicen lo mismo de la caja dard
of Troy but they have all said things about
de Troya pero todos han dicho cosas de
the box how are they going to give him money how are they
la caja que cómo le van a dar dinero que
going to give him money that that guy
cómo le van a dar dinero que ese tío
eats that that guy goes on vacation
come que ese tío se va de vacaciones
how are they going to  give money I'm going
cómo le van a dar dinero me estoy
crazy because they give him money I mean we've
desquiciando porque le dan dinero o sea
heard all these things
todas estas cosas las hemos escuchado
here so yes the thing about the cash register has been what
aquí entonces sí lo de la caja ha sido
this Meles has burned but in a
lo que este meles ha ardido pero de una
brutal way And look at you, the cash register
manera brutal Y fíjate tú que la caja
has 3000 and something euros eh that
tiene 3000 y pico de euros eh que esta
tonight before I go to sleep I have to
noche antes de irme a dormir le tengo
make the transfer to the lawyer
que hacer la transferencia el abogado
for the answer to the lawsuit 3000 and
para la contestación a la demanda 3000 y
something euros I mean the entire cash register tonight I'm
pico de euros O sea la caja esta noche
going to spend it all on the
la voy a gastar entera en la
answer to the
contestación a la
lawsuit a kiss my Manuela love but
demanda un beso mi Manuela corazón pero
no aen if they take away the channels don't understand
no aen si te quitan los canales no enten
tricks they have to deal with
trampas se las tienen que ver con
us with all of us who follow you
nosotros con todos los que te seguimos
a kiss Manuela I'm glad I'm glad that you
un beso Manuela me alegro me alegro que
protect me But well, I know as long as you follow me everywhere eh it's worth it to us I was going to tell you something Oh, the cash register what's happening with the cash register yes I have to spend the cash register tonight if you want I'll show you
me protej Pero bueno se yo con que me
the invoice okay if you want I'll
enseño la factura vale si os queréis os
show you the invoice that tonight
enseño la factura que esta noche esta
tonight I'm paying the lawyer
noche le estoy pagando yo al abogado
before going to bed Look Pio if
antes de acostarme Mira Pio si una
each Spaniard has a peseta but not to m a d
peseta cada español pero no a m a d
they have to is that the lawyer told me the message
tienen que es que me dic el mensaje el
one thing that doesn't Wait a moment
abogado una cosa que no Espérate un
[Music] It's that I ca
[Música]
n't show you the
momento Es que no puedo mostrar la
entire conversation Because if they say
conversación entera Porque si dicen
other things but basically tonight
otras cosas pero básicamente esta noche
before going to bed I'll pay the
antes de irme a la cama le pago al
lawyer the first bill 3000 and some
abogado la primera factura 3000 y pico
turkey if you want I'll show it to you Yes yes they
de pavo si queréis os la enseño Sí sí la
take it out Cruz you take it out you take out the money
sacan Cruz la sacas tú sacas el dinero
You take out the money You take the money out
Tú sacas el dinero Tú sacas el dinero
whenever you want from the cash register So
cuando quieras de la caja Entonces ya
today what's there I have it and ad more
hoy lo que hay ahí lo tengo que y ad más
exactly more or less eh It's 3000 and a bit
justo más o menos eh Son 3000 y poco
3300 I think it's 3000 just more or less just more
3300 creo que son 3000 justo más o menos
or less Well I'm telling you that there's
justo más o menos Pues te digo que que
nothing there I don't know I don't understand why they're
no hay ahí no sé no entiendo por qué les
so angry about something that they're going to do to me
arde tanto una cosa que me van a hacer
you know I don't understand why as if I'm not
sabes No entiendo por qué como si no me
going to buy a car calmly I'm not
voy a comprar un coche tranquilo no me
going to buy a car nor am I going to
voy a comprar un coche ni me voy a
buy a Gucci vest I'm going to
comprar un un chaleco de Gucci voy a
pay for the nonsense that you're doing to me
pagar la tontería que me estáis haciendo
you know  but well I don't know how much
sabes pero bueno Yo no sé Cuánto costará
the attorney will cost that's another thing eh but of
el procurador que esa es otra eh pero
course taking into account that it's a
claro teniendo en cuenta que es un
lawsuit of 8,000 bucks the attorney will
pleito de 8.000 pavos el procurador me
also ask me for whatever he wants anyway It's
pedirá también lo que quiera en fin Es
obvious because when she says well
evidente porque cuando dice ella bueno
there's the other channel where we can do
queda el otro canal donde podemos hacer
the cooking and make food Well she assumes
la cocina y hacer comida Bueno ella da
that she has to go to that
por hecho que se tiene que ir al Canal
new Channel yes let's remember that my dear
ese nuevo sí recordemos que mi querida
Joana Morilla who sends her a kiss
Joana morilla que le mand un besito
from here that I haven't been able to talk to
desde aquí que no he podido hablar con
her because I've been
ella porque he estado cu días
disconnected for days and in bed because Joana
desconectadas y en cama pues Joana
Morilla put in a request
morilla le puso un un requerimiento
first to reach an
primero para para para llegar a una
agreement to portray what Johana
acuerdo que se retratar lo de Johana
Morilla eh what Johana Morilla eh
morilla eh lo de Johana morilla eh
brutal eh I come from the youth to contribute
brutal eh vengo de la chavalería aportar
some support to
tien apoyo al
grandfather ro Livin today we have a live show
abuelo ro Livin hoy tenemos un directo
then in the youth what do I think
luego en la chavalería que me parece
Yesterday was cinema eh the youth eh Yesterday
Ayer fue cine eh la chavalería eh Ayer
was cinema but it's that yesterday we got
fue cine pero es que ayer nos enrollamos
so involved man that I didn't even record a video for the
tanto tío que no grabé ni vídeo para el
main eh in the youth
principal eh en la chavalería
pi yes a
pi si una
p but
p pero
not anytime soon  each one will have their
no dentro de nada cada uno tendrá su
little box a kiss marilu Hey but what
cajita un beso marilu Oye pero que me
are you telling me that Diego Arabal has
estáis diciendo que Diego arabal ha
criticized the box is it true or are you
criticado la caja es verdad o me estáis
lying to me I arrived on time Who
engañando Ho llegué a tiempo Quién ha
was Manui How are you I don't think so because you
sido manui Cómo estás No creo eh porque
often come
muchas veces venís
to María Valencia says Diego p a box
a María Valencia dice Diego p una caja
look there I have a shoe box No
mira ahí tengo una caja de zapatos No
man I'm joking but don't worry
hombre estoy de broma pero que no pase
whoever wants it I have these things
nada el que quiera yo estas cosas lo
down here eh s But I don't
tengo aquí abajo eh s Pero a mí no me no
like to be asking and such because I
me gusta estar pidiendo y tal porque yo
believe that we have to work Hey whoever
creo que que tenemos que trabajar Oye el
wants to give something then give and whoever doesn't
que quiera dar algo pues ya dará y el
want then don't give it no problem
que no quiera pu qu no de no pasa nada
if we're going to continue working the
si nosotros vamos a seguir trabajando
same but oh well man always stop
igual pero bueno hombre siempre
to keep the channel a little bit going and
para para mantener un poquito el canal y
man I'm not going to I'm not
hombre yo no voy a yo para abogados no
going to ask for that if it's true that I'm not for
voy a pedir eso si es verdad que yo para
lawyers
abogados
no I'm not for lawyers because let's
no yo para abogados no porque a
see if I put my foot in it I'll have to
ver si yo meto la pata la tendré que
pay no you're not going to pay me all of
pagar yo no no me vais a pagar todos
you if I put my
vosotros si yo meto la
foot in it all eh
pata todos eh
all the box is already a trend like everything you
todos la caja es ya tendencia como todo
do Javi face the eye
lo que haces Javi carando el ojo cara de
cat face kiss beautiful  How are you?
gato beso guapa Cómo estás
Why aren't they going to pay my lawyers?
Por qué no me van a pagar los abogados
3315 so far that I have donated, let's see
3315 hasta ahora que yo he donado a ver
if all this is of any use, and I know that it will
si sirve para algo todo esto y se que
be with lawsuits, point, contribute
sea con demandas al canto punto aportar
whoever can, please, you, you, urrecha, this
quien pueda por favor tú tú urrecha está
urre, you are crazy, eh, you are
urre estáis loquísimos eh estáis
crazy. I mean, they are not going to, they are not
loquísimo O sea que no me van a que no
going to pay my lawyers. Why,
me van a pagar los abogados Por qué por
why, Diego? I mean, I would like to know
qué Diego O sea me gustaría saber por
why you can charge eh people to
qué tú puedes cobrar eh a la gente para
talk to you on the phone for a little while
que hable contigo por teléfono un ratito
on the 800 or so number that you had on the
en el 800 y pico ese que tenías en el
phone,
teléfono
but I know it's absurd, man, it does
sea pero s que está absurdo tío sí que
n't make sense, I don't pay for a lawyer,
no tiene sentido yo no pago para abogado
no, no, but if you have
no no pero si tienes aquí
signs here, I mean, you had a phone number of 800 or
carteles o sea tenías un teléfono de 800
so, a number that
y pico un número de un número que
cost a fortune for people to call you,
costaba Una pasta a la gente llamarte
but if you have PayPal here, bison, you are
pero si tienes aquí PayPal bison te
missing a post here, you are
falta poner
missing a
aquí te falta porer aquí una
post here, everyone, everyone and you know what that
ucha todos todos y sabéis qué que la
these are things that people don't, eh,
Estos son cosas que la gente no eh
these are things. Look, the other day there, neither
esto son cosas Mira el otro día ahí ni
there nor predicted it, they say this. Look,
lo ahí ni lo vaticinaba dice esto mira
in the past, when when, I don't know when I do
antiguamente cuando cuando no se cuando
n't know.  I put the visa people I'm not going to
no se ponía el visum la gente yo no voy
put a visa there are some that I have
a poner visum hay algunos que tengo yo
here the click saying or Oy Oy How are you going to
aquí los click diciendo o Oy Oy Cómo vas
put a bisom that is stealing then
a poner un bisom eso es robar luego
they put the bisom But this happened from the
ponían el bisom Pero esto pasó desde las
antipodes eh from the antipodes eh
antípodas eh desde las antípodas eh
true with the phone but of course
cierto con lo del teléfono pero claro
but of course how are you going to start saying
pero claro cómo te vas a poner a decir
that you are not going to ask But then all
que no vas a pedir Pero entonces todos
the signs that you have there you are not
los carteles que tienes ahí no estás
asking well Hey well it will be for a lawyer
pidiendo pues Oye pues será para abogado
or it will be for whatever you want what does it matter
o será para lo que tú quieras qué más
I am not asking to be a lawyer I don't piss it's that
da Yo no pido para abogado no meo es que
if you if you had to ask to be a
si tú si tú tuvieras que pedir para
lawyer you have to open a
abogado tienes tienes que abrir unas
few decades more than mine of yabu
cuantas decadas más que las mías de yabu
of the patreon stage it is totally true
de la etapa patreon es totalmente cierto
but this is because these are things that are from
pero esto es porque son cosas que son de
the times of the times and the
las épocas de las épocas y de los
advances or I mean in the past I remember
avances o sea antiguamente yo me acuerdo
that dasas for example I don't remember
que dasas por ejemplo no me acuerdo
who else Dallas was one of the first to
quién más Dallas fue de lo primero que
put patreon and people put p put
puso patreon y la gente pone p pone
patreon so that their lawyers pay I don't
patreon para que paguen sus abogados no
know what I don't know how much and it's like Yes
sé qué no sé cuánto y es como Sí hoy en
nowadays everyone with patreon the
día todo el mundo con patreon lo de los
well you who have not been there at
bueno ustedes que no habéis estado en
that time but listen to me Mazda
esa época pero escúchame hace Mazda
Thank you very much don't you all all
Muchísimas gracias no tien todos todos
are going to put money in a couple of
van a poner caja dentro de un par de
weeks save this click Lili Lili
semanas guardar este click Lili Lili
save this click and send it to me when
guarda este click y me lo mandas cuando
the time comes because it's the same as
llegue el momento porque es igual que
the visum that the patreon that everything in
los visum que el patreon que todo dentro
a couple of weeks a couple of months
de un par de semanas un par de meses
everyone will have a box for whatever
están todos con una caja por lo que sea
and if they don't do it it's because right now
y si no lo hacen es porque ahora mismo
we are recording this clip
estamos grabando este clip
and you know what you of course this This
e ustedes sabéis qué ustedes claro esto
is that it's been a long time in
Esto es que ya hace mucho tiempo pada
Spanish but not to me you have to be clear
español pero no a m a tienen que claro
I wish that the trolls are defended by their
yo deseo que al trolles lo defienda su
lawyer friend I'm sure they will win heads and
amiga la abogada seguro que ganan cara y
praying with laughter heads and praying with laughter
orando de risa cara y orando de risa
pathetic also a nuance that I
patéticos además una un Matiz que le
want to give him what Diego Arrabal said
quiero dar lo que ha dicho Diego arrabal
and with this I have no problem eh let
y con esto que yo no tengo problema eh
him think what he wants and that's it I
que él opine lo que quiera y ya está Yo
think whatever I want about his content too
opino lo que sea de su contenido también
and nothing happens But there is a nuance I
y no pasa nada la Pero hay un Matiz yo
don't ask because I put my foot in it I ask
no pido porque yo meta la pata Yo pido
for boycotts the boycotts
para los boicots los boicots las
persecutions to be able to report all
persecuciones poder denunciar a todos
those who want to report, do you understand me? I
los que quieron denunciar me entiendes o
mean, I've explained very well to the
sea yo he explicado aquí muy bien a la
people here why I'm asking, do you understand, the
gente para qué pido me entiendes la
people are the ones who are here living
gente es la que está aquí viviendo el
day to day with me and people decide if
día a día conmigo y la gente decide si
they think it's good and if they think it's bad and I think it's good to
les parece bien y les parece mal y yo
them, eh, I mean, I
creo que les parece bien eh o sea yo
think that the people, I think that the
creo que a la gente yo creo que a la
people have liked this box, eh.
gente le ha parecido bien esta caja eh
But what am I telling you? This
Pero qué es lo que os digo también este
month has also covered the issue of the
mes ha cubierto el tema de la
response to this guy's lawsuit.
contestación a la demanda de este tío
This month, this month we have filled out the
este mes este mes hemos llenado la
response to this guy's lawsuit. I
contestación a la demanda de este tío la
have it, okay, the next thing is, Okay, when
tengo vale lo próximo Vale cuando cuando
the expenses of this trial are
se cubran los gastos de este juicio que
covered, the box is to
se vaya llenando la caja es ir
sue those who have to
demandando a los que tenemos que
sue, do you understand, the box has been
demandar me entiendes la caja se ha
requested because I can face it if they
pedido por yo puedo hacer frente a que a
sue me, let's see, when there are five
mí me demanden a ver ya cuando van cinco
or six lawsuits, there are a few, they are a
o seis demandas van unas cuantas son un
little bit tedious, okay. But the issue here
poquito pesados vale Pero aquí el tema
is all the lazy people that I want to open, the
es todos los playos que yo quiero abrir
funny thing is that later they don't remember, yes, they
la gracia es que luego no se acuerdan sí
will remember because he saved
se van a acordar porque l me ha guardado
the nines clip for me.  s they are going to remember because
el clip nines s se van a acordar porque
Lili I like that you have your box Javi
Lili me gusta que tengas tu caja Javi
Thank you Patricia Thank you very much
Gracias Patricia Muchas gracias muchas
thank you for that they get angry because you are
gracias por eso se pican porque eres
clear and you tell us what the
claro y nos dice para lo que van los
envious ones are for But Only
envidiosos Pero Solamente les puede
the people I am suing can be bothered by the box I mean there is
molestar la caja las personas a las que
no more eh if
estoy demandando O sea no hay más eh si
you realize no there is no more eh
os dais cuenta no no hay más eh
Only the
Solamente les puede molestar las
people who can be bothered by the box It
personas a las que la caja Solamente les
can only be bothered by the people I
puede molestar a las personas a las que
am suing or those who or those who
estoy demandando o a las que o a las que
defend them there is no more but
le defiendan es que no hay más pero
apart from criticizing that you that you pay
aparte criticar que tú que tú pagues
lawyers But if here it is asked for whatever
abogados Pero si aquí se pide para lo
here it is asked for whatever
que sea sea aquí se pide para lo que sea
Oh for whatever the
Ay para lo que
mind because the first thing I
sea la mente porque yo lo primero que he
thought was that it was not a
pensado es que no fuera una medida
precautionary measure There it is let's remember that Johana
cautelar Ahí está recordemos que Johana
what she asked for was the precautionary measures
lo que pedía era las medidas cautelares
that I don't know that I don't speak to her Eh
que no lo sé que no hablo con ella Eh
This is my assumption right now Neither
Esto es una suposición mía ahora mismo
me either Well I didn't see it
Tampoco yo tampoco Bueno nos lo vi ha
Joana said eh if she hadn't said it
dicho Joana eh si no lo hubiese dicho
but maybe she has PR come or she has
pero a lo mejor ella se le ha PR venir o
had some warning  on YouTube Because
ha tenido algún aviso en YouTube Porque
one thing is YouTube and another thing is the
una cosa es YouTube y otra cosa son los
courts if on YouTube in its day or
juzgados si en YouTube en su día o
claimed in its day it is possible it is possible
reclamó en su día es posible es posible
that some notice has reached him I'll leave it there I do
que algún aviso le haya llegado Ahí lo
n't know because as I say I haven't
dejo No lo sé porque como digo no he
spoken with more theories more theories more
hablado con más teorí más teorías más
theories come on let's read the chat
teorías venga vamos a leer el chat
because there were many theories here What do I do
porque había muchas teorías aquí Qué
with everything when you think what do I do with
hago con todo cuando piens que hago con
everything are you going to close the telesalseo channel
todo vas a cerrar el canal de telesalseo
Well they want to close it down they want to
Bueno me lo quieren cerrar me lo quieren
close it down for what I just saw let's
cerrar por lo que acabo de ver a
see man It is obvious that if someone
ver hombre Es evidente que si alguien
has been telling you this for months if a
lleva meses diciéndote estopo si una
peseta for each Spaniard but not to m a d they have to be
peseta cada español pero no a m a d
true I don't know if you remember
tienen que es verdad no sé si recuerdas
but we your community we collected
pero nosotros tu comunidad t reunimos
money for the lawsuit that you are interested in
dinero para la demanda que te interis
buying your cup money pun let's
las comprarte tu taza dinero pun
remember I will never forget in my life I will
recordemos no se me olvidará en la vida
never forget in my life and there and there we
no se me olvidará en la vida y ahí y ahí
were not like now eh there we go I
no estábamos como ahora eh ahí vamos yo
remember that we were not because
me acuerdo que que no estábamos porque
I remember perfectly even what I
me acuerdo perfectamente incluso de lo
had in the bank at that time I
que tenía en el banco en ese momento yo
eh I remember perfectly urre I
eh me acuerdo perfectamente urre me
remember
acuerdo
perfectly yes yes yes yes
perfectamente sí sí sí sí
and but it's that this  is that so I mean the
y pero es que esto es así O sea la
truth Look the other day ini put it
verdad Mira el otro día ini lo lo puso
eh When I gave to rabar I had to pay
eh Cuando di a rabar le tenga que pagar
Mariló but it's that it's a lot of
Mariló pero es que eso es muchísimo
money Yes That sentence is confirmed that
dinero Si Se confirma esa sentencia que
I believe but it happens that that is the
yo creo que pero pasa que esa es la
civil one first the
civil primero tiene que terminar el
penal has to finish you know but it is many many many
penal sabes pero es muchos muchos muchos
clo that he says No I do not put a box
clo que dice No yo no pongo una caja
Javi if you close a channel they also
Javi si te cierras un canal también
close the prisoner Yes if they close a channel they
cierran el reo Sí si te cierran un canal
close everything yes and you do not stop it's not that they are
te cierran todo sí y no paras es no es
going to close it it must be
que te lo vayan a cerrar es que debe ser
you who does not have much affection No you must not
tú que no tiene mucho cariño No no debes
have much affection so much or rather Loli let's
tener mucho cariño tanto o sea Loli a
see if I understand Loli you can
ver si yo lo entiendo Loli tú puedes
dedicate yourself to what you do there chill
dedicarte a lo que te dedicas ahí chill
not to all the insults you make there And
no a todos los insultos que haces ahí Y
such chill But that people react and
tal chill Pero que la gente reaccione y
all that is not
demás eso no
worth it I mean That we have collaborated with you
vale es decir Que colaboramos contigo
for a long time Never abandoned me but it
desde hace mucho Nunca me abandon pero
is that it is like that but that I think it will be
es que eso es así pero eso yo creo que
for a reason no Not because you are stupid I
será por algo no No porque seáis tonto
think it is because living Things
yo creo que es porque vivir Las cosas
with me you do
conmigo
not hit the chest but you do not know
no das el golpe de pecho pero no sabes
stop stop the thing the thing nowadays is
para para la cosa la cosa hoy en día es
a crime  defamation is a
un delito la difamación hoy en día es un
crime nowadays go to court and
delito preséntate en el juzgado y
report it Loli go to court
denúncialo Loli preséntate en el juzgado
and report it let's see who they give the
y denúncialo a ver a quién le dan la
reason you already have the opportunity you are
razón ya tienes la la oportunidad estás
sued fraudulent strikes still
demandada strikes fraudulentos aú
sacrificing your channel do you realize the
inmolando su canal os dais cuenta de la
lie Thank you very much Josefina
mentira Muchísimas gracias Josefina
Pedreira who just made a
pedreira que acaba de hacer una
contribution to the fund as well and the
aportación a la caja también y y la
mental hallucination that
alucinación mental que en este momento
this boy is suffering at this moment I don't know who to talk to
sufre este chico yo no sé con quién
this boy will talk eh the truth is
hablar hablará este chico eh la verdad
I don't know who he's talking to but whoever
yo no sé con quién habla pero el que le
told him that imagine what
haya dicho eso imaginaros de lo lo que
the people around this boy are like who
rodea la gente que rodea A este chico
doesn't tell him so you don't say t stupidity and
que no le dice para no digas t burrada y
t and t nonsense
t y t tontería
eh yeah a pñ but don't f a d they have to
eh si una pñ pero no m a d tienen que
remember that I also collaborated And that You
recuerdo que colaboré también Y eso Tú
was the Dallas Anica you collaborated and you
era lo de Dallas Anica tú colaboraste y
were for a visit seriously queo of this no
eras para visita serio queo de esto no
maybe you believe it Eh then eh
igual te lo crees Eh entonces eh
possibly possibly
posiblemente posiblemente
medical reports are passed to YouTube
se pasen informes médicos a YouTube
medical reports to YouTube Ah wait you
informe médicos a YouTube Ah espérate lo
say it there but then what  you do And
dices ahí pero después qué haces Y se
start asking for the channels that have been
empiece a pedir los canales que se han
passed I do later
pasado hago después
Loli don't look over there Uh Yes no I didn't
Loli no mires para allá Uh Sí no no he
say what I said I can pass them on
dicho lo que he dicho puedo pasarlos ir
putting all the links of your
poniendo todos los enlaces de vuestros
live shows not cli I can't send the
directos no cli no puedo mandar el
link with the minute but the link of the
enlace con el minuto pero el enlace del
live show as you very well know No I
directo como tú muy bien sabes No yo lo
see it well Loli I see it to you that
veo bien Loli yo lo veo a tien que
when we fill the box you open a
cuando llenemos la caja abres un
maritime container for
contenedor marítimo para demandas
International demands facing The eye and that they
Internacionales carando El ojo y que
continue Burning face crying with laughter face
sigan Ardiendo cara llorando de risa
crying with laughter but let's see when we
cara llorando de risa pero a ver cuando
fill the box to How much do
llenemos la caja a A cuánto creéis
you think we can fill the box of
ustedes que podemos llenar la caja pues
course No but listen to me How much how much do
claro No pero escúchame a Cuánto cuánto
you see a How much do you want to get
veis ustedes un A cuánto queréis llegar
repeat the same thing that you say to her
repite lo mismo que le dices tú a ella
a kiss x thank you very much a kiss a
un beso x muchísimas gracias un beso un
kiss Let's see is that how much we need
beso A ver es que cuánto necesitamos
how much we need how much do you think we
cuánto necesitamos cuánto creéis ustedes
need for everything that we
que necesitamos para todo lo que
want it would be crazy eh it
queremos sea sería sería una locura eh
would be crazy in the sense of chill
sería una locura en el sentido de chill
calm down everyone sued and
tranquilísimo todo el mundo demandado y
then wait for time calmly and for
ya esperar el tiempo tranquilito y que
justice you know to decide Manu says
la justicia sabes decida Manu dice
30,000 aini  says 15000 man to I think
30.000 aini dice 15000 hombre a yo creo
that one Although it is an outrage But that
queun Aunque es una barbaridad Pero que
these things cost like this to be
las cosas estas cuestan así lo lo para
able to for everything that we want for
poder para todo lo que queremos para
everything that I would like each and every
todo lo que me gustaría a todos y cada
one of them eh man I think that about
uno de ellos eh hombre Yo creo que unos
20 or 30 It would be more or less logical urre
20 o 30 Sería más o menos lo lógico urre
heart What
corazón Qué
about because what they do to you is unfair And
tal porque es injusto lo que te hacen Y
we feel close to you like our
nos sentimos cercanos a ti como nuestro
channel It is of trust and
canal Es de confianza y de
entertainment and with dear and respect that we
entretenimiento y con caro y respeto que
all have for you who make up your
te tenemos todos que hacemos tu
community face with many
comunidad cara con muchas
thanks I think that I simply
gracias yo creo que simplemente os
explain the situation to you and I tell you look I would
expongo la situación y os digo mira me
like this how do you see it And you
gustaría esto cómo lo veis Y ustedes
are the ones who are living day to
sois los que estáis viviendo el día a
day with me and those who say Well then we
día conmigo y los que decir Bueno pues
want to do this, be it this is not
queremos hacer esto sea esto no es una
something for me to do this is
cosa para que yo la haga esto es una
something that we are going to do all be you do
cosa que vamos a hacer todos sea ustedes
not want to sue Loli sue
no queréis demandar a Loli demandar a
one of them send the other be it this is
uno dem mandar al otro sea esto es una
something that we do the community the link
cosa que hacemos la comunidad el enlace
of the Channel and the live with the minute and
del Canal y del directo con el minuto y
together with them I can put together the reality
junto con ellos puedo juntar la realidad
with with everything says they allude talking about
con con todo dice aluden hablando de
lawsuits and trials go to  up Yes let's see
demandas y juici ir para arriba Sí a ver
this one from Joan Plas what happens eh for those of you who do
este de Joan plas lo que pasa eh para el
n't understand a little about how
que no entendáis un poco de lo Cómo
this works, the one from Johan Planas what
funciona esto el de Johan planas lo que
happens is that eh the lawyers cost more
pasa es que eh los abogados cuestan más
and the solicitors cost more
caro y los procuradores cuestan más caro
But because the colleague has put
Pero porque el colega ha puesto
880,000 So when we are in a
880.000 Entonces cuando estamos en un
lawsuit for 880,000 there is a table in the
pleito de 880.000 hay una tabla en el
bar association eh what are
colegio de los abogados eh que es son
the costs Okay then the lawyers
las costas Vale entonces los abogados
the solicitors And that well they charge
los procuradores Y eso pues cobran en
based on what they ask for that is why he did not
función a lo que pidan por eso él no
ask for money in the first Plate so that it would
pedía dinero en el primer Plate para que
cost him less to risk less you
le costara menos para arriesgarse menos
understand but removing the one from Joan
me entiendes pero quitando el de Joan
Plana removing the one from Johan Plana the
plana quitando el de Johan plana los
other lawsuits the ones in which I want to sue
otros pleitos los que yo quiero demandar
one sue the other the lawsuit that
a uno demandar al otro la demanda que
we have filed against Loli okay or
nosotros le hemos puesto a Loli vale o
so the lawsuit that I have filed against
sea la demanda que yo le he puesto a
Loli practically with these 3000 and something
Loli prácticamente con estos 3000 y pico
would be covered you understand and if I
estaría cubierta me entiendes Y si le
want to file another one with another 3000 with
quiero poner otra con otros 3000 con
less it would also be covered you
menos estaría puesta también me
understand with 30,000  crosses everyone
entiendes con 30.000 los crues a todos
with 30,000 I think we're pretty
con 30.000 yo creo que estamos bastante
chill Yes Anika of course obviously if he
chill Sí anika claro evidentemente si le
if he loses this and doesn't accept him
si él si él pierde este y no le acepta
in the compensation he has to pay
en la indemnización él tiene que pagar
the costs that go according to what he
las costas que van en función a lo que
has asked for a lot of money that
ha pedido mucho mucho dinero que se lo
he pays to my lawyer But what am I
paga él a mi abogado Pero qué es lo que
telling you eh him removing this from Johan
os digo eh el quitando este de Johan
Planas this barbarity that he has done of
planas esta barbaridad que ha hecho de
putting 880,000 the rest the rest of
poner 880.000 el resto el resto de
playon doesn't cost us that much money eh And
playon no nos cuesta tanto dinero eh Y
I'm going to always tell you what what I have
yo os voy a ir diciendo siempre lo que
spent what it has
lo que me he gastado lo que me ha
cost me family today I had to pay
costado familia hoy he tenido que pagar
1000 in family attorneys tomorrow I
1000 en en procuradores familia mañana
have to pay 15,000 because they have
tengo que pagar 15,000 porque me han
sentenced me whatever it is I'm going to
condenado todo lo que sea os lo voy a ir
tell you that obviously the sentences I'm
diciendo que evidentemente las condenas
not going to take them from here if they
No las voy a [__] de aquí si me
sentence me I opened it to respond to you
condenan me lo abrí para responderte
to respond to whoever messed with me
para responder a quien se metía conmigo
No well I honestly the day I
No pues yo de verdad que el día que me
opened it I didn't think that today I would be
lo abrí no pensaba que hoy estaría
making this video because I thought that you all
haciendo este vídeo porque pensaba que
would forget me and  left alone but
me fuerais olvidado y dejado en paz pero
since it couldn't be no And the law is very
como no ha podido ser no Y la ley es muy
slow Well
lenta Pues
also eh can I stop answering If
también eh puedo dejar de responder Si
not if there's no one to answer
no si no hay a nadie a quien responder
no but the thing is that I love the thing about I'm going to
no pero es que me encanta lo de voy a
stop answering and that's how he's
dejar de responder y es como está
answering but apart from that he says no no the
respondiendo pero aparte dice no no la
law says tesa and the lawyer who is no
ley dice tesa y el abogado que no es
pushover tesa The thing is that
moco de pavo tesa Es que lo que pasa es
these things cost a lot a
que estas cosas cuestan muchísimo
lot of money a lot of money man I mean I
muchísimo dinero muchísimo tío o sea yo
think they shouldn't cost so much eh I mean I
creo que no deberían costar tanto eh o
think it should cost you money
sea yo creo que debería costarte pasta
if they condemn you obviously but issues
si te condenan evidentemente pero temas
of issues of minutes and things and things like
de temas de de minutas y cosas y cosas
that the truth is it seems like an
de esas la verdad me parece una
outrage of Expensive I respect eh I respect
barbaridad de Caro respeto eh respeto
everyone all the professions and everything and it will
todos lo todas las profesiones y todo lo
have its meaning But it seems to me
y que tendrá su sentido Pero me parecen
these things seem very expensive
me parecen muy caras estas
so that Peppa wanted money
cosas as que que Peppa quería dinero
Antonio Peppa only wants money and Peppa
Antonio Peppa solo quiere dinero e Peppa
for money she doesn't care and Antonio because it's
por dinero le da igual e Antonio porque
her her livelihood others because it's her
es su su sustento otros porque es su
livelihood did you doubt that this could happen to you did you
sustento dudabas que te pudiera pasar
doubt it because I'm
esto lo dudabas porque yo me lo estoy
thinking about it but I think that if you
pensando pero yo creo que si tú te
move forward Well the same eh move forward that I  I told you in
avanzas Pues al igual eh avanza que yo
advance that I'm not going to take down the
me avance que yo no te voy a tirar el
channel Loli, nor am I going to take down the channel, nor am I
canal Loli ni te voy a tirar el canal ni
going to, nor am I going to do anything to you, the
te voy a ni te voy a a a nada que yo lo
only thing I want is for you to show up for
único que quiero es que te presentes en
this
este
procedure, okay, show up and
procedimiento vale que te presentes y
pay, he says my father was a lawyer and
que pagues dice mi padre era abogado y
self-employed and an office has a lot of
autónomo y un despacho tiene muchísimos
expenses, I imagine it makes sense
gastos me imagino que tendrá su sentido
that things cost a lot, that's an outrage,
que las cosas cuesten Esa esa barbaridad
but well, I'll explain it to you so that
pero bueno yo os lo explico para que
you know, dean, you're either stupid
ustedes lo sepáis la deano tú eres tonto
or they've done the four to you, let's see, it
o te han hecho las cuatro a ver un
would be a crime if I put it to you in some
delito sería si te lo pusiera en unos eh
live shows where you don't talk about me and you lie, which I
directos donde no hablas de mí y mientes
could, or you humiliate me, which I
cosa que podría o me humillas cosa que
could also do without it being a
también podría hacerlo sin que fuera
crime, no, you have a lot, you're either
delito no que tienes mogollón tú eres
stupid or they've eaten the four, man,
tonto o te han comido las cuatro tío
when you eat the 4 you're very
cuando se come las 4 se tiene mucha
hungry and you don't understand anything, you do
hambre y ya uno no se entera de nada ya
n't know if you're eating or training, let's
no sabe si está comiendo o trenando a
see, boy, I said it clearly, send
ver chico que lo he dicho claro mandar
a medical report, take those clips and For that
un informe médico [__] esos clip y Por
reason, you loser, you're a loser. Ah,
ese motivo pringado que eres un pring Ah
okay, I'm a
vale soy un
loser, urre. Says, well, urre, it's
pringao urre dice Bueno urre condenarte
impossible to condemn you, time  time you never know
imposible tiempo al tiempo nunca se sabe
urre you never know Look at the first one that
urre nunca se sabe Mira la primera eso
is very subjective, I mean You realize eh
es muy subjetivo o sea Tú date cuenta eh
that there are sentences I don't tell you and you
que hay sentencias no te digo y ti
80,000 but they can I know by
80.000 pero te pueden yo que sé por
figure more Look at Nauter's it is one that I
cifra más Mira la de nauter es una que
put because it is that dic It is not that it is not
yo pongo porque es que dic No es que no
quantified, the YouTube thing is already
está cuantificado lo de YouTube ya está
quantified There are a lot of 100 it goes
cuantificado Hay un montón de 100 me va
to the attorney, I do not read it e Ah Well
al procurador no lo lailo e Ah Pues
we need another 1000 Well we need
necesitamos otros 1000 Pues necesitamos
another 1000 because the attorney
otros 1000 porque el procurador me lo
will ask me for it right now not as soon as he goes to
pedirá ya mismo no en cuanto vaya a
answer me he will ask for the money the
responderme pedirá el dinero el
attorney do not listen to me it is overwhelming
procurador no escúchame es agobiar
people economically of course it is
económicamente a la gente claro es
official
aficial
e This is what Rosi did or that I
e Esto es lo que hacía Rosi o que
drag with Antonio David listen to me mm I was
arrasco con Antonio David escúchame mm
going to tell you something and I slipped up Ah they
te iba a decir algo y se me ha ido Ah
say that YouTube is not quantified I do not
que dicen que no está cuantificado lo de
know what YouTube is already
YouTube no sé qué YouTube ya está
quantified There are a lot of
cuantificado Hay un montón de sentencias
these sentences about the right to honor of
de estas del derecho al honor de
youtubers Look at Nauter's Nauter
youtubers Mira la de de nauter nauter
for making videos to wismichu okay they
por hacerle vídeos a wismichu vale
put it in  videos for two of videos
metieron vídeos durante dos de vídeos
that belonged to 2 years and the insults
que pertenecían a 2 años y los insultos
were for you to see them you [ __ ]
eran para que tú los Vieras cabronazo
monger I don't know what you know And they condemn because
monger no sé qué sabes Y condenan porque
you can't insult unless it's
tú no puedes insultar a no ser que sea
in a context I don't know how much it's
dentro de un contexto no sé qué cuanto
worth And they condemn you for those insults
vale Y te condenan por por esos insultos
trust you monger [ __ ] 1000 euros But oh
fíate tu monger cabronazo 1000 eur Pero
well But it's more than the lawyer's expense
bueno Pero ya es más el gasto de abogado
and the ass that he gives you than the
y el por culo que te da que que la
sentence Santi we'll talk about that later in
condena Santi eso lo hablaremos luego en
the kids' room people the gossip but the
la chavalería gente el salseo pero el
supreme court has not condemned Dallas
supremo no ha condenado a a Dallas lo
the provincial court condemned him and
condenó la audiencia provincial y por
that's why the result has been so fast
eso ha sido tan rápido el resultado
because here in Spain I don't know if in
porque aquí en España el no sé si en los
other countries too but the
otros países también pero el tribunal
supreme court It's not another instance as such In other words, there
supremo No es otra instancia como tal O
has to be a
sea tú tiene que haber un interés
cassation interest or in other words, another instance where the
casacional o sea otra instancia donde se
whole case is reviewed it's in the
revisa todo el caso es en la audiencia
provincial court there they see the whole case
provincial ahí se ven todo el caso
again and they review it well and
entero otra vez y lo y lo repasan bien y
such the supreme court has to meet some
tal el supremo tiene que cumplir unos
requirements that I don't fully understand
requisitos que yo no término de entender
how it works But it has to have a
cómo va Pero tiene que tener interés
cassation interest not for them to transmit the
casacional no para que te transmitan el
appeal to you  when you when you send an
recurso cuando tú cuando tú mandas un
appeal to the Supreme Court they have to
recurso al supremo te lo tienen que
admit it and once they admit it they
admitir y una vez que te lo admiten lo
review it or not I mean they review it and they rule in your favor
revisan o no O sea lo revisan y te dan
or they don't rule in your favor okay But maybe they wo
la razón o no te la dan vale Pero a lo
n't admit it which is what
mejor no te lo admiten que es lo que ha
happened in Dallas what
pasado a Dallas a Dallas lo que le ha
happened to Dallas is that they didn't admit the
pasado es que no le han admitido el
appeal you know I wouldn't have
recurso me entiendes Yo no lo hubiera
appealed that because it was also of no
recorrido eso porque es que tampoco
interest to the Supreme Court it doesn't
tenía interés casacional a mí no me
seem to me it seems to me like a crazy
parece a mí me parece una burrada de
sentence in the sense of the amount it
Sentencia en el sentido de la cuantía me
seems like an outrage I understand that it's
parece una barbaridad entiendo que será
because of the uh repercussions he has not
por la eh repercusión que él tiene no
because of the diffusion he has
por la difusión que él tiene
but what happened is that they didn't
pero pero lo que ha pasado es que no
admit the appeal But well we'll
admiten el recurso Pero bueno eso lo
talk about that later we'll talk about that later I mean
hablamos luego lo hablamos luego o sea
but in reality the sentence is from
pero en realidad la sentencia es la de
the second instance the
la segunda instancia la de la audiencia
provincial court That's the one that is now final you
provincial Esa es la que ahora es firme
are a loser loser find out find
eres un pringado pringado entérate
out eh fraudulent fraudulent
entérate eh fraudulento fraudulento eres
you are the whole thing the fake hair the fake eyes
tú entero el pelo falso los ojos falsos
the fake nose and the rest is the eyes and
la nariz falsa y de resto es los ojos y
the fake nose the fake eyes and the
la nariz falsa los ojos falsos y la
fake nose It's that from that  Javi there is
nariz falsa Es que de aquel Javi no
nothing left because how do you put on filters
queda nada porque como te pones filtros
so that your double chin can't be seen
para que no se te vea la
filter so that your double chin can't be seen
papada filtro para que no se te vea la
But how do you do that I love them
papada Pero cómo se hace eso los quiero
eh
eh
What do you think the others are like
A qué te crees que los demás son como
your friends who use you as a sucker
tus amiguis que te utilizan de pringao
because alne weighs everything Lila or Lali or
porque alne pesa todo la Lila o Lali o
whatever the [ __ ] all those people are called They are
como [__] se llame toda esa gente Te
using you, sucker you find that you are
está usando pringado encuentras que eres
a bit of a sucker when you are acting like a
un poco pringado cuando estás haciendo
fool every day and every night
el tonto todos los días y todas las
on your channel and well that's for
noches en tu canal y bueno eso de
now because I assure you that this by
momento porque te aseguro yo que esto a
naming the days at the expense of Loli
nombrándolos los días a Costa de Loli
Huertas I am not proving the family pension to you
huertas no os estoy probando la pensión
What do you think of this do you think that
familia Qué os parece esto creéis que
this for example if I sue her she will
esto por ejemplo si yo la demando me
pay me or how do you see it do you think it's
pagará o cómo lo veis ustedes creéis
shameful disgusting and besides if you're not
vergonzoso asqueroso y aparte si no
worth it you say so if you leave as a
vales lo dices si te vas de
forklift driver you go to another job like someone who is
carretillero te vas a otro trabajo como
not worth it for a job and they try
el que no vale para un trabajo y prueban
another and if you're not good enough and you've fallen into the
otro y si no sirves y te has caído en la
deepest [ __ ] that a person can fall into which
[__] más profunda que puede caer una
is the one in the  that you are
persona que es la de en la que tú estás
You screw man you've earned it you're
Te jodes tío te ganado te lo estás
earning it every day well family we are in
ganando cada día pues familia estamos en
the because we haven't earned it the truth is that
la porque no lo hemos ganado la verdad
a wonderful live performance that
que una maravilla de directo que nos ha
Huerta has dedicated to us we're going to move on to the
dedicado Huerta vamos a pasar a lo
next
siguiente
[Music]
[Música]